Guide to the Atlantic Philanthropies Archives, 1982-2017.
Atlantic Philanthropies Archives,
- Series IV: Grant Files
  - Subseries F: Northern Ireland grant files, 1977-2018
    - QUB - general, 1999. File 2, 1999-2002 (Box 173, Folder 18-19)
      - #11836. International Centre for Research on SOC (System-on-Chip) and Advanced Micro Wireless Integration (SPUR 2), 2003-2007, 2009 (Box 144, Folder 5)
        File number N 12/36
        Computer Science
      - #11836. SOCAM. File 2, 2004, 2007, 2010 (Box 144, Folder 6-7)
      - #11839. Centre for Climate, the Environment, and Chronology (SPUR 2), 2003-2007, 2009 (Box 144, Folder 8-9)
        File number N 12/38
        Environmental Education
        Physical/Earth Sciences
      - #12737. Aging sector scoping study, 2004-05-2004-10 (Box 144, Folder 10)
        Ageing Research
      - #12737. Aging Sector scoping study. Review of the Age sector in N.I., 2004, 2006 (Box 144, Folder 11-12)
        File number N 26/8/4
      - #13589. Comparative research on community based peace-building (Kieran McEvoy), 2003-2006 (Box 144, Folder 13)
        File number N 28/7/6
        McEvoy, Kieran
      - #13762. Age sector advocacy policy research and support, 2000, 2005-2010 (Box 144, Folder 14-15)
        File number N 26/8/11
      - #13963. Omagh bomb victim. Clare Gallagher - music therapy course, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 16)
        File number N 12/39
        Gallagher, Clare
        Founding Chairman
      - #13963. Omagh bomb victim. Clare Gallagher Scholarship, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 17)
      - #14252. Establishment of a center of excellence, 2006-2008 (Box 144, Folder 18)
        File number N 28/7/13. Grant not found in FLUXX
      - #14255. Planning shared education in specialist schools, 2006-2007 (Box 144, Folder 19)
      - #14255. Mainstreaming collaboration in education. File 1, 2005-2007 (Box 145, Folder 1-2)
        File number N 28/7/14
      - #14255. Mainstreaming collaboration in education. File 2, 2006-2007 (Box 145, Folder 3)
      - #14255. Mainstreaming collaboration in education. File 3, 2006 (Box 145, Folder 4)
      - #14348. Improving children's lives: an interdisciplinary research initiative at Queen's University Belfast. Effective interventions for children (Paul Connolly). File 1, 2007-2013 (Box 145, Folder 5)
        File number N 27/8/32
        Connolly, Paul, 1966-
      - #14348. Improving children's lives: an interdisciplinary research initiative at Queen's University Belfast. Effective interventions for children (Paul Connolly). File 2, 2012-2014 (Box 145, Folder 6)
      - #14348. Improving children's lives: an interdisciplinary research initiative at Queen's University, Belfast, 2008-06-27 (Box 145, Folder 7)
      - #15031. Promoting shared education in Northern Ireland. Develop a standard methodology for assessing the extent to which school development proposals comply with "A Shared Future", 2006-2007 (Box 145, Folder 8)
      - #15031. Promoting shared education in Northern Ireland. School of Education (Tony Gallagher), 2006-2007 (Box 145, Folder 9)
        File number N 28/7/21
        Gallagher, Tony
        Queen's University of Belfast. School of Education
      - #15583. Sharing education (main grant), 2007-2009, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 10-11)
        File number N 28/7/24
        - Sharing Education: GMTV, BBC Newsline 13.30, DTR/Cool fm news/U105 news, 2007-09-24; CD-5288 (Box 145, Folder 11)
      - #15709. Shared education program baseline and research, 2008-2010 (Box 145, Folder 12)
      - #15919. Budget analysis - rights in NI, 2007-2008, 2011 (Box 145, Folder 13)
      - #15919. Budget analysis - rights in NI, 2002, 2004, 2007-2011 (Box 145, Folder 14)
        File number N 28/7/28
      - #16390. Joint Learning Initiative on Children and Ethnic Diversity, 2007-2012 (Box 145, Folder 15)
        File number N 27/8/35
      - #16510. Shared Education Project II, 2007-2012 (Box 145, Folder 16-17)
        File number N 28/7/39
      - #16510. Promoting Shared Education: open program, 2009-2010 (Box 145, Folder 18)
        File number N 28/7/35. Folder includes a progress report and correspondence.
      - #16938. Pilot for the Stirling Oregon Northern Ireland Cognitive Study (SONICS), 2007-2008 (Box 145, Folder 19)
        File number N 26/8/43
        Mobile communications
      - #18590. Strengthening practice and supporting advocacy, 2010-2011 (Box 145, Folder 20)
        File number N 28/7/62
      - #21720. Final evaluation of the Advancing Children's Rights objective in NI, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 21)
        File number N 28/7/77
        Evaluation
      - #22604. Sustainability Models of Practice, 2013-2014 (Box 146, Folder 1)
        File number N 0/0/17.
      - #25142. QUB/Arts Council Seamus Heaney Legacy Initiative, 2014 (Box 146, Folder 2)
        File number N 0/0/18. No grant-related documents, proposal only.
      - #27122. (Untitled), 2012 (Box 146, Folder 3)
        File number N 28/7/72. Papers reference grant #27122 as grant to QUB Foundation; however, FLUXX lists as a designated gift to Mutual Engine Hose Co. Eng. 1
    - Reminiscence Network Northern Ireland, 2006-2011, 2014
      Reminiscence Network Northern Ireland
      Hospice Care
      - #15925. Development of reminiscence centre. File 1, 2007-2009, 2011, 2014 (Box 146, Folder 4)
        File number N 26/8/36
      - #15925. Development of reminiscence centre. File 2, 2006-2011 (Box 146, Folder 5-6)
    - Rural Community Network, 1996-2014; Rural Community Network (Northern Ireland)
      Rural Community Network (Northern Ireland)
      - #7419 (#96-44). Rural Community Development Unit. File 1, 1996-2000 (Box 146, Folder 7-8)
        File number N 19/3
      - #7419 (#96-44). Rural Community Development Unit. File 2, 2000-2003 (Box 146, Folder 9-10)
      - #8473. Low community infrastructure program. File 1, 1996, 1999-2002 (Box 146, Folder 11)
        File number N 19/3/1
      - #8473. Low community infrastructure program. Weak infrastructure. File 2, 2000-2009 (Box 146, Folder 12-13)
      - #8473. Low community infrastructure program. Reports, 2003, 2005, 2009 (Box 146, Folder 14)
      - #12072. Core support (exit grant), 2002, 2004-2007 (Box 146, Folder 15-16)
        File number N 19/3/2
        - Participatory Rural Planning: resources, methodology, analysis, 2007; CD-5298 (Box 146, Folder 16)
      - #16074. Skills and empowerment for rural older people, 2008, 2011-2014 (Box 146, Folder 17)
        File number N 26/8/38
      - #16074. "Skills for Solutions", 2006-2011 (Box 147, Folder 1-2)
      - #16074. "Skills for Solutions" supplemental, 2004, 2007-2008, 2012 (Box 147, Folder 3)
        File number N 26/8/38 (2)
        - Rural Community Estates Program: Practice to Policy Study, 2007; DVD-3465 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Scotch-Irish Trust of Ulster, 1993-1995, 1997
      Scotch-Irish Trust of Ulster
      Genealogy
      - #7204 (#93-38). Feasibility study, 1993-1995, 1997 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Social Economy Agency, 1998-2007; Social Economy Agency (Northern Ireland)
      Social Economy Agency (Northern Ireland)
      - Social Economy Agency, 2005 (Box 147, Folder 5)
        File number N 18/33. Proposal only, no grant-related documents.
      - #9620. Phoenix Project for Ex-Prisoners. File 1, 2000-2001, 2003 (Box 147, Folder 6)
        File number N 18/33
      - #9620. Phoenix Project for Ex-Prisoners. File 2, 1998-2006 (Box 147, Folder 7-8)
      - #12257. Social capital (support for ex-prisoners loan fund), 2003-2007 (Box 147, Folder 9)
        File number N 18/33/1
        - Terry Boyle: First Leaves of Autumn, 2007; CD-5277 (Box 147, Folder 9)
          File number N 18/33/1. Musical CD
    - Social Security Agency, 2011-2013, 2015; Northern Ireland Social Security Agency
      Northern Ireland Social Security Agency
      - #20349. Innovation Fund, 2011-2013, 2015 (Box 147, Folder 10-11)
        File number N 26/8/73
    - South Tyrone Empowerment Programme, 2002-2003, 2005-2013
      South Tyrone Empowerment Programme
      - #14249. Capacity building support. Developing infrastructure Â for minority ethnic community, 2006-2012 (Box 147, Folder 12-13)
        File number N 28/7/15
        Labor Rights
      - #14794. Planning grant to support migrant communities, 2006 (Box 147, Folder 14)
      - #14794. Planning grant to support migrant rights, 2002-2003, 2005-2006 (Box 147, Folder 15)
        File number N 28/7/18
      - #16116. BELONG: Family Support Program for Black and Minority Ethnic Children. File 1, 2008-2010, 2013 (Box 147, Folder 16-17)
        File number N 27/8/38
      - #16116. BELONG: Family Support Program for Black and Minority Ethnic Children. File 2, 2009-2011 (Box 148, Folder 1-2)
      - #16116. BELONG: Family Support Program for Black and Minority Ethnic Children. File 3, 2011-2012 (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - #20218. Migrant support - final, 2012 (Box 148, Folder 4)
        File number N 28/7/80
    - Springwell Centre, 2004-2009, 2011
      Springwell Center
      - T4A Springwell - Lurgan community engagement, 2005, 2007 (Box 148, Folder 5-6)
        File number N 27/8/15/1. No grant-related documents.
      - Appendices, 2007 (Box 148, Folder 7-8)
      - #14055. Lurgan community engagement site - planning grant, 2004-2009 (Box 148, Folder 9-10)
        File number N 27/8/15
      - #14055. Lurgan community engagement site - planning grant, 2005-2006 (Box 148, Folder 11)
      - #15155. Together 4 all - supplementary planning grant, 2006-2007 (Box 148, Folder 12)
      - #15155. Together 4 All - supplementary planning grant. Lurgan community engagement, 2005-2007 (Box 148, Folder 13-14)
        File number N 27/8/15/2
      - #15854. Â Planning grant for BME (Black and Minority Ethnic Children strand), 2007 (Box 148, Folder 15)
      - #15854. T4A- planning grant for BME. File 1, 2005, 2007-2008 (Box 148, Folder 16-17)
        File number N 27/8/26.
      - #15854. T4A- planning grant for BME. File 2, 2007-2008 (Box 148, Folder 18)
        File number N 27/8/26
      - #15854. T4A- planning grant for BME. File 3, 2008-2009, 2011 (Box 148, Folder 19)
      - #15856. Additional planning grant, 2007 (Box 148, Folder 20)
      - #15856. T4A additional planning grant, 2007-2008 (Box 148, Folder 21)
        File number N 27/8/25
    - St. Columb's Park House, 1997-2004, 2006
      St. Columb's Park House
      - Inter Isles Project, 1999-08-05 (Box 149, Folder 1)
        File number N 16/12. No grant-related documents.
      - St. Columb's Park House. Loose materials, 1998-2002 (Box 149, Folder 2)
        File number N 17/40. No grant-related documents.
      - #8471. Education for Citizenship Support Program. File 1, 1997-2000 (Box 149, Folder 3)
        File number N 17/40
        Boys/Girls Clubs
      - #8471. Education for Citizenship Support Program. File 2, 2001-2004, 2006 (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - #10481. Inter-Isles Forum for Political Youth Wings, 2001-2004, 2006 (Box 149, Folder 5)
        File number N 17/40/1
    - Stratagem (NI) Ltd., 2007-2014
      Stratagem (NI) Ltd.
      - #16438. Advocacy and lobbying support program, 2007-2008 (Box 149, Folder 6)
      - #16438. Advocacy and lobby support program, 2007-2009 (Box 149, Folder 7)
        File number N 26/8/34.
      - #17233. Advocacy and lobbying support for aging program, 2009 (Box 149, Folder 8)
      - #17233. Advocacy and lobbying support for aging program, 2009-2011 (Box 149, Folder 9)
        File number N 26/8/51
      - #17519. Providing support, advice, and information to Northern Ireland grantees, 2011-2014 (Box 149, Folder 10)
        File number N 26/8/71
    - Suffolk Lenadoon Interface Group, 2005-2012; Suffolk-Lenadoon Interface Group
      Suffolk-Lenadoon Interface Group
      - #14250. Â Area based peace-building plan for Suffolk/Lenadoon, 2006 (Box 149, Folder 11)
      - #14250. Integrated peace-building plan, 2005-2007 (Box 149, Folder 12)
        File number N 28/7/12
      - #14251. Peace-Building in Suffolk and Lenadoon, 2005-2009 (Box 149, Folder 13-15)
        File number N 28/7/10
      - #14251. Peace-Building in Suffolk and Lenadoon. File 1, 2006-2008, 2011 (Box 149, Folder 16-18)
      - #14251. Peace-Building in Suffolk and Lenadoon. File 2, 2007-2009 (Box 150, Folder 1-3)
      - #14251. Peace-Building in Suffolk and Lenadoon. Atlantic Philanthropies progress report submitted: 23rd November 2007, 2007 (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - #17584; #17961. Phase 2 area peace-building, 2009, 2009-2011 (Box 150, Folder 5-8)
        File number N 28/7/43
      - #17584; #17961. External evaluation reports, 2009 (Box 150, Folder 9)
      - #21231. Suffolk and Lenadoon Interface Group (SLIG), 2011-2012 (Box 150, Folder 10)
        File number N 28/7/70
    - Tara Counselling and Personal Development Centre, 2000-2001, 2003
      Tara Counselling and Personal Development Centre
      Counseling and Support Groups
      - Counselling and Personal Development Center. Business plan. Lynx Business Services, June 2000, 2000-06 (Box 150, Folder 11)
      - Counselling and Personal Development Center. Loose subject material, Undated (Box 150, Folder 12)
      - #8367. Building extension, 2000-2001, 2003 (Box 150, Folder 13)
        File number N 17/17/39.
    - Together 4 All Limited, 2007-2014; Springwell Centre
      Together 4 All Limited
      Springwell Centre
      - #14342. Together 4 All - Integrated Children's Services. File 1, 2007-2014 (Box 150, Folder 14-16)
        File number N 27/8/15/1
      - #14342. Together 4 All - Integrated Children's Services. File 2, 2007-2014 (Box 150, Folder 17-18)
      - #14342. Together 4 All - Integrated Children's Services. File 3, 2007-2014 (Box 150, Folder 19-20)
      - #14342. Together 4 All issue, 2010 (Box 151, Folder 1)
        File number N 27/8/15/1/1.
    - Ulster People's College, 1989, 1995-2003
      Ulster People's College
      - Core costs and annual report, 1998-2000 (Box 151, Folder 2)
        File number N 17/18/2. No grant-related documents.
      - #7480 (#97-08). Leadership development, 1995-2002 (Box 151, Folder 3)
        File number N 17/18
        Northern Ireland Women's Coalition
      - #7480 (#97-08). Leadership development. Women and leadership, 1996-1997, 2003 (Box 151, Folder 4)
        File number N 20/3
      - #7480 (#97-08). Supplemental materials, 1989, 1995, 1998 (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - #7578 (#97-105). Northern Ireland Women's Coalition. Research, 1997-1999 (Box 151, Folder 6)
        File number N 17/18/1
        Political Organizations
    - Ulster Quaker Service Committee, 1996-2001
      Ulster Quaker Service Committee
      - #7542 (#97-69). Reconciliation project. Kairos project, 1997 (Box 151, Folder 7)
      - #7542 (#97-69). Reconciliation project, 1996-1999 (Box 151, Folder 8)
        File number N 17/17
      - #7667 (#98-34). Core support. Kairos project, 1998-2001 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Understanding Conflict Trust, 1996-2007
      Understanding Conflict Trust
      - Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 151, Folder 10)
        File number N 17/24. Includes financial statements, an evaluation report, and grantee-related materials.
      - #7700 (#98-69). Core support. To April 2001, File 1, 1996-2002 (Box 151, Folder 11-12)
        File number N 17/24
      - #7700 (#98-69). Core support. To April 2001, File 2, 1996-2002 (Box 151, Folder 13)
      - #11918. Future Ways: community relations consultancy and research. File 1, 1991, 2002-2007 (Box 151, Folder 14-15)
        File number N 17/24/1.
      - #11918. Future Ways: community relations consultancy and research. File 2, 2002-2007 (Box 151, Folder 16)
        File number N 17/24/1
      - #11918. Supplemental materials, 2003-2004 (Box 151, Folder 17)
    - University of Massachusetts Foundation, 1996-1997
      University of Massachusetts Foundation
      - #7522 (#97-49). Northern Ireland/South Africa conference, 1996-1997 (Box 151, Folder 18)
    - University of Newcastle upon Tyne, 2006-2007
      University of Newcastle upon Tyne
      - "Hearts and Minds - Deliberative Polling - 01/02/07" VHS tapes, 2007-02-01; VHS-11626 (Box 152, Folder 1)
        File number N 28/7/22. Folder contains two VHS tapes; the blue tape is unlabeled and undated.
      - #15293. Deliberative poll on shared education in Northern Ireland, 2006-2007 (Box 152, Folder 2)
        File number N 28/7/22
        - Deliberative Polling, Hearts and Minds, 2007-02-01; DVD-3466 (Box 152, Folder 2)
      - #15293. Deliberative poll on shared education in Northern Ireland, 2006 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - University of Ulster Foundation, 1991-2013
      - Assessment meeting, 20 April 1999, 1999 (Box 152, Folder 4)
      - Centre for the Study of Conflict, 1994, 1996-1999 (Box 152, Folder 5)
        University of Ulster. Centre for the Study of Conflict
      - Centre for the Study of Conflict: general, 1991-1997 (Box 152, Folder 6)
      - Geophysical Techniques in Coastal Zone Science. Submission to Joint Infrastructure Fund, 2000-04 (Box 168, Folder 31-32)
      - Publications, 1996, 1998-1999 (Box 152, Folder 7)
        Folder contains magazines, proposals, and reports.
      - Support Program for University Research: Business Plans, 2000-08 (Box 168, Folder 28)
      - Springvale Project: Community Outreach Center. Payment request to private donor, 2000-08-18 (Box 168, Folder 29)
      - Vice chancellor's retirement, 1998-1999 (Box 152, Folder 8)
      - Magee College academic development plan, 1997, 1999 (Box 152, Folder 9)
        File number N 11/1. No grant documents.
      - Springvale, 1998-1999 (Box 152, Folder 10)
        File number N 11/3. No grant documents.
      - Springvale, 1995-1996 (Box 152, Folder 11)
      - Springvale project. File 2. Nov '95-Dec '96, 1995-11-1996-12 (Box 152, Folder 12-13)
      - Springvale Millennium application, 1996 (Box 152, Folder 14)
      - Springvale project documents, 1993-1999 (Box 152, Folder 15)
      - Springvale project. Jan '97 - Dec. '97, 1994, 1996-1997 (Box 152, Folder 16)
        File number N 11/3
      - Springvale. Part 1, 1994-1998 (Box 152, Folder 17-18)
        File number N 11/3a
      - Springvale Educational Village. Part 2, 1997-1999 (Box 152, Folder 19-20)
      - Springvale Educational Village. Part 3, 1999 (Box 153, Folder 1)
      - EO (Equal Opportunity) in University of Ulster, 1997 (Box 153, Folder 2)
        File number N 11/5. No grant documents.
      - NI Life and Times Survey - press cuttings; reports/papers/articles etc., 1998-2001 (Box 153, Folder 3)
        File number N 11/6. No grant documents.
      - Northern Ireland Life and Times Survey, 1998-1999, 1999-2004 (Box 153, Folder 4)
        - Northern Ireland Life and Times Survey, 1998 data, 1999-03; FD-942 (Box 153, Folder 4)
          File number N 11/6
        - Northern Ireland Life and Times Survey, 1999 data, 2000-04; FD-953 (Box 153, Folder 4)
      - NI Life and Times Survey - loose miscellaneous papers, 1997 (Box 153, Folder 5)
        File number N 11/6. Includes budget projections, correspondence, and proposal.
      - UUJ (University of Ulster Jordanstown) - Learning Resource Center, 1997-1999 (Box 153, Folder 6)
        File number N 11/7 (a). No grant documents. Materials refer to the Jordanstown campus.
      - UU - John Hume Center, 1998-01 (Box 153, Folder 7)
        File number N 11/9. No grant documents.
      - Higher Bridges project, 1997-1998 (Box 153, Folder 8)
        File number N 11/11. Includes correspondence and progress reports only.
      - UU - Research Office, 1999-2000 (Box 153, Folder 9)
        File number N 11/18. Includes correspondence only.
      - UUM Student Center, 1999-2000 (Box 153, Folder 10)
        File number N 11/20. Includes correspondence only. Materials refer to the Magee College campus.
      - Research Village - UUM (University of Ulster, Magee College), 1999-2000 (Box 153, Folder 11)
        File number N 11/21. Includes subject material and a summary report.
      - UUM (University of Ulster, Magee College) Student housing, 1999-09-23 (Box 153, Folder 12)
        File number N 11/22. Includes correspondence only. Materials refer to the Magee College campus.
      - UU - priorities to 2010, 1999-2000, 2002 (Box 153, Folder 13)
        File number N 11/25. Includes correspondence and subject material.
      - UUM (University of Ulster, Magee College) - general, 2000-2001 (Box 153, Folder 14)
        File number N 11/27. Includes correspondence and subject material. Materials refer to the Magee College campus.
      - UUC (University of Ulster Coleraine) - general, 2000 (Box 153, Folder 15)
        File number N 11/28. Includes correspondence only. Materials refer to Coleraine campus.
      - SPUR (Support Program for University Research) bids, 2000, 2003 (Box 153, Folder 16)
        File number N 11/29. No grant documents.
      - Centre for Molecular Biosciences. Inaugural meeting of the International Scientific Advisory Board. March 20-21, 2003, 2003-03 (Box 168, Folder 30)
        File number N 11/31
      - UU - York Street strategic land purchase, 2000-2001 (Box 153, Folder 17)
        File number N 11/32. No grant documents, correspondence only.
      - ARK II materials, 2002-2003 (Box 153, Folder 18)
        File number N 11/33. No grant documents, includes subject material and an annual report.
      - Report on the Community Audits Carried Out by the University of Ulster at Magee, 1993-1997, 1998-02 (Box 153, Folder 19)
        File number N 19/1. No grant documents.
      - #7116 (#92-11). Centre for the Study of Conflict: United Nations feasibility study, 1991-1994, 1996-1998 (Box 153, Folder 20)
      - #7185 (#93-19). Centre for the Study of Conflict: interfaith marriages in Northern Ireland- institutional attitudes, 1993-1994, 1996 (Box 153, Folder 21)
      - #7270 (#94-41). Centre for the Study of Conflict: research project- role of religion and churches in modern Ireland north and south, 1994-1996 (Box 153, Folder 22)
      - #7286 (#94-58). Springvale Project: developing a compelling case, 1994-1995 (Box 153, Folder 23)
      - #7311 (#95-20). Northern Ireland Educational Foundation: Centre for Voluntary Action Studies, 1995, 1998 (Box 153, Folder 24)
        University of Ulster. Centre for Voluntary Action Studies
      - #7362 (#95-73). Aberfoyle Estate acquisition. Masterplan, 1996-2000 (Box 153, Folder 25)
        File number N 11/4
      - #7362 (#95-73). Appendix D - Aberfoyle Estate masterplan, 1999 (Box 153, Folder 26)
      - #7362 (#95-73). Land purchase: Aberfoyle Estate, next to Magee College, Derry, 1995-1999 (Box 153, Folder 27)
      - #7414 (#96-39); #7286 (#94-58). Community Outreach Center. File 1. 2/12/97-23/1998, 1997-1998, 2000-2001 (Box 153, Folder 28-29)
        File number N 11/3/2
      - #7414 (#96-39) and #7286 (#94-58). Community Outreach Center. File 2, 1994, 1996-1997, 1999-2003 (Box 153, Folder 30)
      - #7414 (#96-39). Community Outreach Centre, Springvale campus, 1996, 1999-2003 (Box 153, Folder 31)
      - #7501 (#97-28). Springvale campus. UU consultancy, 1995, 1997-1998, 2006 (Box 154, Folder 1)
        File number N 11/3/1
      - #7501 (#97-28). Springvale Campus- supplementary materials, 1997-1999 (Box 154, Folder 2)
      - #7537 (#97-64). Centre for the Study of Conflict. Northern Ireland Educational Foundation - action research., 1996-2000 (Box 154, Folder 3)
        Pre-collegiate Education and Teacher Development
      - #7537 (#97-64). Center for the Study of Conflict. NIEF (Northern Ireland Educational Foundation) /UU Development Office, 1995-2004 (Box 154, Folder 4)
        File number N 11/2
      - #7640 (#98-9). N.I. Life and Times Survey, 1997-2001 (Box 154, Folder 5-6)
      - #7643 (#98-12). Technology and Software Incubation Center, 1997-2001 (Box 154, Folder 7)
        File number N 11/10
        Business and Industry